Professor Joseph Werlin Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Press Clippings
  - Glass Negatives (Box 10, Folder 2)